[(Document(id='fbbf3927-7095-4a46-817f-4934f956dd38', metadata={'age_range': '5-8', 'category': 'Adventure', 'moral': 'Courage and kindness can turn strangers into best friends.', 'created_at': '2026-05-06T08:10:48.969978+00:00', 'run_id': 'fbbf3927-7095-4a46-817f-4934f956dd38', 'title': 'The Brave Little Fox'}, page_content='In a lush green forest, there lived a brave little fox named Felix. He was always curious and loved exploring.\n\nOne day, Felix heard a soft whimper coming from the old oak tree. He approached carefully and found a trapped baby bird.\n\nFelix used his sharp teeth to gently break the twigs holding the bird. They became best friends instantly.\n\nFrom that day on, Felix and the bird explored the forest together, helping any animals in need.'), 1.281754970550537), (Document(id='c9ab8c0e-fba2-405e-a8b0-ef2bc3a57842', metadata={'category': 'Sci-Fi', 'age_range': '6-10', 'created_at': '2026-05-06T08:10:48.969978+00:00', 'title': "Luna's Space Journey", 'moral': "Dream big, and you'll find friends in the most unexpected places.", 'run_id': 'c9ab8c0e-fba2-405e-a8b0-ef2bc3a57842'}, page_content='Luna was a bright young girl who dreamed of visiting the stars. She built a shiny rocket ship in her backyard.\n\nWith a loud countdown, she blasted off into the sparkling galaxy. Planets zoomed past her window in brilliant colors.\n\nShe met a friendly alien who taught her how to dance in zero gravity. They laughed and played among the asteroids.\n\nLuna returned home safely, knowing the universe was full of wonderful surprises and new friends.'), 1.8227773904800415), (Document(id='49388e03-fc9e-4fa9-912a-cd7f94397bfc', metadata={'age_range': '5-9', 'run_id': '49388e03-fc9e-4fa9-912a-cd7f94397bfc', 'moral': 'Practicality is often more valuable than beauty.', 'category': 'Fable', 'created_at': '2026-05-06T08:10:48.969978+00:00', 'title': 'The Ant and the Diamond'}, page_content="An ant was carrying a piece of sugar when he found a glowing diamond. It was beautiful but very heavy.\n\nHe tried to lift it, but couldn't move it even an inch. Other ants passed by, carrying their food.\n\nThe ant realized that the diamond, while pretty, couldn't feed his family. He left it and picked up his sugar.\n\nWhen winter came, he was happy and well-fed, knowing he had made the right choice."), 1.9606854915618896)]
